<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Caroline Taymor</title><link>https://tech.taymor.io/</link><description>Recent content on Caroline Taymor</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 22:20:06 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tech.taymor.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Give Tech Tech Talks</title><link>https://tech.taymor.io/posts/why-give-tech-talks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 22:20:06 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tech.taymor.io/posts/why-give-tech-talks/</guid><description>Last year, I set myself the goal of giving my first technical talk at a conference. I exceeded that goal in spades. I&amp;rsquo;ve given my talk &amp;ldquo;Getting Unstuck: Using the Scientific Method for Debugging&amp;rdquo; 5 times, gotten paid to speak, and 600-700 people have seen my talk in person or on video. I also burned out on speaking, and resolved to stop giving talks. Then I changed my mind.
Why speak?</description></item><item><title>Getting Unstuck: Using the Scientific Method For Debugging</title><link>https://tech.taymor.io/talks/getting-unstuck/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech.taymor.io/talks/getting-unstuck/</guid><description>Have you ever gotten really stuck while trying to understand the cause of a bug? Thinking of your debugging session as a science experiment, and using the scientific method can help you make progress again. Come and learn how to adapt the scientific method (the process used for scientific research) to get past that stuck place and find the cause of bugs or production incidents. You’ll walk away with a great new tool to keep you calm and focused in the face of inevitable bugs.</description></item><item><title>Getting Unstuck - Reference Guide</title><link>https://tech.taymor.io/posts/getting-unstuck/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech.taymor.io/posts/getting-unstuck/</guid><description>Are you excited to try using the scientific method for debugging? This is a short reference sheet to refer back to the next time you get stuck in a debugging session, to make the most of the scientific method framework.
This guide comes from my talk &amp;ldquo;Getting Unstuck: Using the Scientific Method for Debugging&amp;rdquo;. Slides can be found here. Video of the talk is coming soon.
Gather existing knowledge Write down what you know.</description></item><item><title>Deploying a blog with Hugo, TravisCI, and Google App Engine</title><link>https://tech.taymor.io/posts/deploying-a-blog-with-hugo-travis-and-gae/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:02:19 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tech.taymor.io/posts/deploying-a-blog-with-hugo-travis-and-gae/</guid><description>Because I wanted to start blogging, I recently moved tech.taymor.io from a couple of static html and scss files* to a static site with a blog generated with Hugo, deployed with Google App Engine. I hit a few snags trying to automate this site with TravisCI and Google App Engine, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share my process.
Build a Hugo app, make it work locally I&amp;rsquo;ll handwave over this a bit.</description></item></channel></rss>